CD4+ T cells drive immune regulation — but a screen alone can't tell you what's druggable.
We joined the GWT screen with external public databases into one verifiable method.
Two independent funnels — readiness and drug-deliverability — intersect on five core targets.
Adjust a weight, reset it, search PLCG1 — the ranking reacts live; the evidence never does.
Every target has its own dossier — effect size, downstream breadth, cross-donor robustness, all inspectable.
Side by side, the five core targets show distinct evidence strength and risk trade-offs.
Switch to the clinician's view: concept, disease, drug, population genetics, expression — strong effect is neither safety nor clinical efficacy.
Change a condition or threshold — the figure updates live, proving context-sensitivity.
Open Targets re-verifies all 55, STRING recovers known partners, an HIV screen lines up too.
The targets most valuable to researchers are often the ones clinicians must watch most closely.
From 22M cells to 7,249 targets — the full curation and analysis pipeline, laid out.
The gallery is publication-ready, the docs explain operation, and the API lets other teams reuse our evidence directly.
We close on provenance — versions, coverage, and the source behind every conclusion, all traceable.